http://www.saint-peters.com/privacy

Username or
Password ?
(403) 938-4261 This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
PrivacyWe collect personal information from our members and donors in the regular course of being the church. We are committed to collecting only the information we need to minister to our town. We also commit to secure the information we keep. This page answers some of your most frequently asked questions, and lets you know exactly how we're protecting the information you entrust to us.
What personal information do you collect about me?
As you interact with St. Peter's Church Okotoks, we may collect the following information from you:
General information
to keep you informed about the work of St. Peter's Okotoks.
Name
Address
Postal Code
Phone Number
Email Address
Ministry information
to keep you informed about ministries you may engage or serve in.
Date of Birth/Age
Gender
Interests
Financial Information
If you donate to support the work of the Kingdom through St. Peter's Church Okotoks we keep your general information as above and a record of your donations in order to issue you a Charitable Tax Receipt at year end.
If you donate to support St. Peter's Church using a credit card, we use a secure provider (Helcim)  based in Calgary. We store the same information as a donation by cheque or Interac e-Transfer. We never see your card details.
Web browsing Information
Please refer to our in-depth policy at the bottom of this page
How do you use this information?
We use this information to carry out the work of the church. Please see our in-depth Privacy Policy below
How do you store this information?
We keep all personal information in our church software Elvanto. It is password protected and access is limited to the people needed to complete a particular task.
Sharing of Personal Information with Third Parties
We do not share your personal information with any third parties.
For A More In-Depth Description of our Privacy Policy:
View Our In-Depth Privacy Policy
For more information on privacy and information protection in Alberta:
AlbertaOffice of the Information and Privacy Commissioner of Alberta410, 9925 - 109 Street, Edmonton, Alberta T5K 2J8Phone: (780) 422-6860Toll Free: 1-888-878-4044Email: generalinfo@oipc.ab.caWeb Site: http://www.oipc.ab.ca
Please Consider Giving To Our Church Using One Of The Methods Below×ModalPlease make your donations through your online banking provider and send to give@stpo.ca. We have auto-deposit turned on so there is no need for a security password. Thank you for your generosity. St. Peter’s Anglican Church
ServicesSundays   10:00am-11:45pmShare Us With Your FriendsFacebookTwitterLinkedinPinterestThublrGetpocketRedditVKContactPhone Us Or Send Us A Message
Home
Sermons
Prayer
Lectionary
Local ChurchesInformation
About Us
Privacy
Give
